[
  {
    "Front": "βαθύς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: dyb"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βαίνω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: går"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βάλλω",
    "Back": " vb. ureg.: kaster"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βάρβαρος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: barbar"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βαρύς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: tung"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βασιλεύς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: konge"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βέλτιστος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: bedst"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βελτίων",
    "Back": " adj. 3: bedre"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βία",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: vold"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βίος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: liv"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βλάπτω",
    "Back": " vb.: skader"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βλέπω",
    "Back": " vb.: ser"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βοάω",
    "Back": " vb.: råber"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βοήθεια",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: hjælp"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βοηθέω",
    "Back": " vb.: hjælper"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βουλεύω",
    "Back": " vb.: giver råd; (med.) rådslår"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βουλή",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: råd; rådsforsamling"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βούλοµαι",
    "Back": " vb. ureg. dep.: vil"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βοῦς",
    "Back": " sb. 3 m.: okse"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βραδύς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: langsom"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βραχύς",
    "Back": " adj. 3: kort"
  },
  {
    "Front": "βωµός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: alter"
  }
]